Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - B
        - Brown, Kathy - I appreciate, 1995; SR-13395; Brown, Kathy (Box 201)
          Catalog # CR-360; A-side Matrix # CR-360-A
          Cutting Records
        - Brown, Mel - The wizard, 1968; SR-13396; Brown, Mel (Box 201)
          Catalog # AS-9169; A-side Matrix # AS 9169 A
          Impulse!
        - Brown, Michael - Dancing to your music, 1983; SR-13397; Brown, Michael (Box 201)
          Catalog # 4Z9 04068; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-04068-5-AA
          Estate Record Corporation
        - Brown, O'Chi - Whenever you need somebody, 1985; SR-13398; Brown, O'Chi (Box 201)
          Catalog # 884 572-1; A-side Matrix # 884-572-1-AS ES
        - Brown, Peter - Do you wanna get funky with me; Dance with me, 1990; SR-13399; Brown, Peter (Box 201)
          Catalog # HCL 2218; A-side Matrix # HCL-2218-A
        - Brown, Peter - (Love is just) the game, 1984; SR-13400; Brown, Peter (Box 201)
          Catalog # 44-05102; A-side Matrix # XSS1169783-1A
        - Brown, Peter - Overnight sensation, 1983; SR-13401; Brown, Peter (Box 201)
          Catalog # JD-13518; A-side Matrix # PD-1-3518-A-1
        - Brown, Peter - Do ya wanna get funky with me, 1977; SR-13402; Brown, Peter (Box 201)
          Catalog # TKD-35; A-side Matrix # TKD35A
        - Brown, Peter - Crank it up (funk town), 1979; SR-13403; Brown, Peter (Box 201)
          Catalog # TKD-151; A-side Matrix # TKD151A
        - Brown, Peter - Baby gets high; Shall we dance, 1982; SR-13404; Brown, Peter (Box 201)
          In same jacket as # SR-13405. 2 copies
          Catalog # JD-13357; A-side Matrix # PD13357A
        - Brown, Peter - Baby gets high; Shall we dance, 1982; SR-13405; Brown, Peter (Box 201)
          In same jacket as # SR-13404. 2 copies
        - Brown, Randy - Welcome to my room, 1978; SR-13406; Brown, Randy (Box 201)
          Catalog # RRLP 9005; A-side Matrix # RRLP 9005 AS(RE-3)
          Parachutes Records
        - Brown, Sharon - I specialize in love, 1982; SR-13407; Brown, Sharon (Box 201)
          Catalog # PRO-7416-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7416-A-1
        - Brown, Sharon - I specialize in love, 1982; SR-13408; Brown, Sharon (Box 201)
          Catalog # PRO-7006; A-side Matrix # PRO-7006A-1
        - Brown, Sharon - You got me where I want to be, 1983; SR-13409; Brown, Sharon (Box 201)
          Catalog # PRO-7035-DJ; A-side Matrix # PRO-7035-A
        - Brown, Sheree - You'll be dancing all night, 1981; SR-13410; Brown, Sheree (Box 201)
          Catalog # SPRO-9665; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9665-97348A
        - Brown, Shirley - Urgent, 1983; SR-13411; Brown, Shirley (Box 201)
          Catalog # 812 989-1; A-side Matrix # 812 989 12 57507 C PRCC1-1A
        - Brown, Shirley - Same time, same place, 1981; SR-13412; Brown, Shirley (Box 201)
          Catalog # TCD-124-DJ; A-side Matrix # TCD-124-AM-C-1S
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Brown, Shirley - Women to women, 1974; SR-13442; Brown, Shirley (Box 201)
          Catalog # SXE 002; A-side Matrix # DM B-8686 A-1
        - Brown Smith & Grey - Carabongo, 2001; SR-13413; Brown Smith & Grey (Box 201)
          Catalog # 057-00825; A-side Matrix # B043450-01 A1 HL
          Audiopharm
          Hanover, Germany
        - Brown, William - Shining; Come on and go with me, 1982; SR-13414; Brown, William (Box 201)
          Catalog # HCI-12-1001; A-side Matrix # HC-12-1001-A
          Houston Connection Recording Corporation
        - Brown, Yvonne - Goin' down; King of the groove, 1982; SR-13415; Brown, Yvonne (Box 201)
          Catalog # 79903; A-side Matrix # 79903-A
          Montage Records
        - Blake, Paul - Every posse get flat, 1985; SR-13416; Blake, Paul; Bloodfire Posse (Box 201)
          Catalog # RAS 7011; A-side Matrix # RAS-7011-A
          RAS Records Inc.
        - Browne, Tom - Love approach, 1980; SR-13417; Browne, Tom (Box 201)
          Catalog # GRP 5008; A-side Matrix # GRP 5008 SB CP3
        - Browne, Tom - Cruisin', 1983; SR-13418; Browne, Tom (Box 201)
          Catalog # ADP-9140; A-side Matrix # ADP-9140-5A
        - Browne, Tom - Yours truly, 1981; SR-13419; Browne, Tom (Box 201)
          Catalog # GRP 5507; A-side Matrix # GRP 5507 SA
        - Brownmark - Next time, 1988; SR-13420; Brownmark (Box 201)
          Catalog # 4601MG; A-side Matrix # 4601-MGA-67968-67953-RE1-67970
        - Brownmark - Bang bang, 1989; SR-13421; Brownmark (Box 201)
          Catalog # L33-17913; A-side Matrix # MOT-9090-BG-4
        - Brownside - Gang related, 1994; SR-13422; Brownside (Box 201)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0240; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0240A
        - Brownstone - Pass the lovin', 1994; SR-13423; Brownstone (Box 201)
          Catalog # EAS 77576; A-side Matrix # XSS-77576-A-1A
          MJJ Music
        - Brunson, Tyrone - Fresh, 1984; SR-13424; Brunson, Tyrone (Box 201)
          In same jacket as # SR-13425. 2 copies
          Catalog # 4Z9 04951; A-side Matrix # AB 429-04951-3
          Believe In A Dream Records
        - Brunson, Tyrone - Fresh, 1984; SR-13425; Brunson, Tyrone (Box 201)
          In same jacket as # SR-13424. 2 copies
        - Brunson, Tyrone - The method, 1986; SR-13426; Brunson, Tyrone (Box 201)
          Catalog # L33-17214; A-side Matrix # MCA-5810-553
        - Brunson, Tyrone - Love Triangle, 1987; SR-13427; Brunson, Tyrone; Adams, Gayle (Box 201)
          Catalog # MCA-23712; A-side Matrix # MCA-6442-F2J3
        - Brunson, Tyrone - Sticky situation, 1982; SR-13428; Brunson, Tyrone (Box 201)
          In same jacket as # SR-13429. Different discs
          Catalog # 4Z9 03512; A-side Matrix # AB 4Z9 03512-3
        - Brunson, Tyrone - Sticky situation, 1982; SR-13429; Brunson, Tyrone (Box 201)
          In same jacket as # SR-13428. Different discs
          Catalog # 4Z9 03512; A-side Matrix # AA 4Z9 03512-5
        - Brunson, Tyrone - The Smurf, 1982; SR-13430; Brunson, Tyrone (Box 201)
          Catalog # 4Z9 03166; A-side Matrix # AB-429-03166-3
        - Bryant, Sharon - Body talk, 1990; SR-13431; Bryant, Sharon (Box 201)
          Catalog # 873 599-1; A-side Matrix # 873599-1-AS-HUB
          Wing Records
        - Brydge - Dangerous; Club banger; I never thought, 2004; SR-13432; Brydge (Box 201)
          Catalog # BBM 023; A-side Matrix # BBM-023-A
        - Bryson, Peabo - Positive, 1988; SR-13433; Bryson, Peabo (Box 201)
          Catalog # 60753-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60753-1-A
        - Bryson, Peabo - There's nothin' out there, 1985; SR-13434; Bryson, Peabo (Box 201)
          Catalog # ED 5072; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5072-A-1
        - Bryson, Peabo - Without you (love theme from Leonard part 6), 1987; SR-13435; Bryson, Peabo; Belle, Regina (Box 201)
          Catalog # ED 5275; A-side Matrix # ST ED- 5275A-1
        - Bryson, Peabo - Take no prisoners (in the game of love), 1985; SR-13436; Bryson, Peabo (Box 202)
          Catalog # ED 5063; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66901-A-1
        - B.S.O. Research - Genuine electric funk machine EP, 1998; SR-13437; B.S.O. Research (Box 202)
          Catalog # HAND 049 T; A-side Matrix # HAND 049 A-1-1
          Hard Hands
        - BT - Love, peace and grease (Disc one), 1997; SR-13443; BT (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13444. Double album
          Catalog # 0-43956; A-side Matrix # 0-43956-A-SR1
          Kinectic Records
        - BT - Love, peace and grease (Disc two), 1997; SR-13444; BT (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13443. Double album
          Catalog # 0-43956; A-side Matrix # 0-43956-C-SR1
        - B.T. Express - Star child (spirit of the night); This must be the night for love, 1982; SR-13445; B.T. Express; Robinson, William (Box 202)
          Catalog # 4Z9 03247; A-side Matrix # AC-429-03247-3
          Coast to Coast
        - B.T. Express - Let me be the one; Midnight beat, 1980; SR-13446; B.T. Express (Box 202)
          Catalog # 43-60518; A-side Matrix # XSS 168517-1F
        - B.T. Express - Does it feel good, 1980; SR-13447; B.T. Express (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13448. 2 copies
          Catalog # AS 817; A-side Matrix # XSS 167685-1B
        - B.T. Express - Does it feel good, 1980; SR-13448; B.T. Express (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13447. 2 copies
        - B.T. Express - 1980, 1980; SR-13449; B.T. Express (Box 202)
          Catalog # JC 36333; A-side Matrix # AL36333-1H
        - B.T. Express - Non-stop, 1975; SR-13450; B.T. Express (Box 202)
          Catalog # RS 41001; A-side Matrix # RS 41001-A-3
          Roadshow
          Hempstead, New York
        - BTX - This jam is black, 1991; SR-13451; BTX (Box 202)
          Catalog # FMS 62378; A-side Matrix # FMS-62378-A
        - Buari - Koko si; I'm ready, 1978; SR-13452; Buari (Box 202)
          Catalog # MD9000; A-side Matrix # MD 9000A
          Makossa International Records
        - Buck, Kathy - Don't beat around the bush, 1983; SR-13498; Buck, Kathy (Box 202)
          Catalog # BZ-1101; A-side Matrix # 606-A
          Buzz Records
        - Buck, Kathy - Don't beat around the bush, 1983; SR-13453; Buck, Kathy` (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13454. 2 copies
        - Buck, Kathy - Don't beat around the bush, 1983; SR-13454; Buck, Kathy` (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13453. 2 copies
        - Buckner & Garcia - Pac-Man fever, 1981; SR-13455; Buckner & Garcia (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13456. 2 copies
          Catalog # 44 02762; A-side Matrix # XSS-169984-1B
        - Buckner & Garcia - Pac-Man fever, 1981; SR-13456; Buckner & Garcia (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13455. 2 copies
        - Buckshot LeFonque - Selections from Buckshot LeFonque, 1994; SR-13457; Buckshot LeFonque (Box 202)
          Catalog # CAS 6566; A-side Matrix # XSS 6566-A
        - Buckshot LeFonque - Breakfast @ Denny's, 1994; SR-13458; Buckshot LeFonque (Box 202)
          Catalog # CAS 6576; A-side Matrix # XSS 6576-A
        - Buckshot LeFonque - Breakfast @ Denny's, 1994; SR-13459; Buckshot LeFonque (Box 202)
          Catalog # 44 77509; A-side Matrix # XSS 77509-A
        - Buda Hedz - If ya swing, 1995; SR-13460; Buda Hedz (Box 202)
          Catalog # 100-ML; A-side Matrix # 100-ML-A
          Miff Records
          Long Island City, New York
        - Buda Hedz - If ya swing, 1995; SR-13461; Buda Hedz (Box 202)
        - Budda Boys - Got to survive (Livin' in the Ghetto), 1985; SR-13462; Budda Boys; Starr, Jumar (Box 202)
          Catalog # OTR-200; A-side Matrix # OTR 200 A
          On Time Records
        - Budden, Joe - Not your average Joe, 2004; SR-13463; Budden, Joe; DJ Kayslay; Fat Joe; Joe (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13464. 2 copies
          Catalog # DEFR 16078; A-side Matrix # B0002710-11
        - Budden, Joe - Not your average Joe, 2004; SR-13464; Budden, Joe; DJ Kayslay; Fat Joe; Joe (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13463. 2 copies
        - Budden, Joe - Gangsta party, 2005; SR-13465; Budden, Joe; Nate Dogg (Box 202)
          Catalog # DEFR 16324-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16324-1A
        - Budden, Joe - Body hot, 2004; SR-13466; Budden, Joe (Box 202)
          Catalog # DEFR 16046-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16046-1A
        - Buddy Miles Express - Booger bear, 1974; SR-13467; Buddy Miles Express (Box 202)
          Catalog # AL 32694; A-side Matrix # 1-PAL-32694-1C
        - Buggers - The Bugger Groove, 1984; SR-13468; Buggers (Box 202)
          Catalog # A-92; A-side Matrix # A-92-A
          Manhole Record Co.
        - Bugnon, Alex - Head over heels, 1990; SR-13469; Bugnon, Alex (Box 202)
          Catalog # D1-75615; A-side Matrix # D1-1-75615-Z3
          Orpheus Records
        - Bukem, LTJ - Sunrain, 2000; SR-13470; Bukem, LTJ; Elliot (Box 202)
          Catalog # GLRSIN001V; A-side Matrix # GLRSIN 001V A-1-1
          Good Looking Recordings
          Watford, United Kingdom
        - Bullet - I'm Billy Jean, SR-13471; Bullet (Box 202)
          Catalog # EW-770; A-side Matrix # EW 770A-RE-1-1-2
          Earwax
        - Bullet Proof Space Travelers - Built to last (Disc one), 2001; SR-13472; Bullet Proof Space Travelers (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13473. Double album
          Catalog # SR8200; A-side Matrix # STY-1-48200 A
          Stray Records
        - Bullet Proof Space Travelers - Built to last (Disc two), 2001; SR-13473; Bullet Proof Space Travelers (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13472. Double album
          Catalog # SR8200; A-side Matrix # STY-1-48200 C
        - Bulostin, Nicolas - Let me be crazy, 2003; SR-13478; Bulostin, Nicolas; McCalla, Noel (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # GRAPES 001 A
          Catalog # GRAPE 001; A-side Matrix # GRAPE 001
        - Bum on the Carpet - Mood Swing, 2004; SR-13474; Bum on the Carpet (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13475. 2 copies
          Catalog # DG 1 001; A-side Matrix # 55303 1A DG 1 001
          Dopeness Galore Records
        - Bum on the Carpet - Mood Swing, 2004; SR-13475; Bum on the Carpet (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13474. 2 copies
        - Bumblebee Unlimited - Lady bug, 1978; SR-13476; Bumblebee Unlimited (Box 202)
          Catalog # RG-218; A-side Matrix # RG-218-RE-2
          Red Greg Records
        - Bumblebee Unlimited - Sting like a bee, 1979; SR-13477; Bumblebee Unlimited (Box 202)
          Catalog # AFL1-3407; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3407A-1
        - Bumblebee Unlimited - The bumble bee rap, 1981; SR-13479; Bumblebee Unlimited (Box 202)
          Catalog # SG 343; A-side Matrix # SG-343-A-1
        - Bumble B.H.E. - Pain, 1995; SR-13480; Bumble B.H.E. (Box 202)
          Catalog # 12-PO129; A-side Matrix # 12PO129A
          380 Recordings
        - Bumforhire - I need a b--ch; Saturday; Club 2000, 1994; SR-13481; Bumforhire; Mood II Swing (Box 202)
          Catalog # CR-325; A-side Matrix # CR325 EAST
        - Bump J - Move around, 2005; SR-13482; Bump J (Box 202)
          Catalog # PR 301711; A-side Matrix # ST-A-93700 A-1
        - Bump J - Pushaman; Move around, 2005; SR-13483; Bump J; West, Kanye (Box 202)
          Catalog # PR 301809; A-side Matrix # ST-A-93793-A-1
        - G Squad - Doctor Doom (part 1 & 2); Shit's real, 1997; SR-13484; G Squad (Box 202)
          Catalog # BS001; A-side Matrix # BS 001 A-01-01-1
          Bump 'N' Sway
        - Bumpy Knuckles - A part of my life; Devious mind, 1999; SR-13485; Bumpy Knuckles; DJ Premier (Box 202)
          Catalog # KJacFP99; A-side Matrix # FP-99-A
          Street Pop
        - B.U.M.S. - Take a look around, 1995; SR-13486; B.U.M.S.; Brothas Unda Madness (Box 202)
          Catalog # SPRO 50880; A-side Matrix # SPRO 50880-A
        - B.U.M.S. - Elevation (free my mind); 6 figures and up, 1994; SR-13487; B.U.M.S.; Brothas Unda Madness (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13488. 2 copies
          Catalog # SPRO 50831; A-side Matrix # SPRO-50831-A
        - B.U.M.S. - Elevation (free my mind); 6 figures and up, 1994; SR-13488; B.U.M.S.; Brothas Unda Madness (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13487. 2 copies
        - B.U.M.S. - Lyfe'N'Tyme (Disc one), 1995; SR-13489; B.U.M.S.; Brothas Unda Madness (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13490. Double album
          Catalog # P1 53886; A-side Matrix # P1-53886-1
        - B.U.M.S. - Lyfe'N'Tyme (Disc two), 1995; SR-13490; B.U.M.S.; Brothas Unda Madness (Box 202)
          In same jacket as # SR-13489. Double album
          Catalog # P1 53886; A-side Matrix # P1-53886-3
        - Bunch, Sekou - Pretty baby, 1982; SR-13491; Bunch, Sekou (Box 202)
          Catalog # SH 592; A-side Matrix # VID 243A
        - Bunch, Sekou - Can't stop lovin' you, 1982; SR-13492; Bunch, Sekou (Box 202)
          Catalog # SH-583; A-side Matrix # VID-234-A
        - Buonocore, Nino - Una citta tra le mani, 1988; SR-13493; Buonocore, Nino (Box 202)
          Catalog # 7902041; A-side Matrix # 7902041-A-12-2-88
        - Burch, Vernon - Never can find a way (hot love); Dr. Do it good, 1979; SR-13494; Burch, Vernon (Box 202)
          Catalog # CCD 20017 DJ; A-side Matrix # CCD-20017-AS-CPI
          Chocolate City
        - Burch, Vernon - Playing hard to get, 1982; SR-13495; Burch, Vernon (Box 203)
          Catalog # SPRO-1001; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1001-G-1
          Spector Records International
          Coral Gables, Florida
        - Burch, Vernon - Do it to me, 1981; SR-13496; Burch, Vernon (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13497. 2 copies
          Catalog # SPRO-00018; A-side Matrix # SRI-00018A F3
        - Burch, Vernon - Do it to me, 1981; SR-13497; Burch, Vernon (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13496. 2 copies
        - Burdon, Eric - Spill the wine, 1970; SR-13499; Burdon, Eric; War (Box 203)
          Catalog # PW-37109; A-side Matrix # PW 37109AS-1E
          LAX Records
        - Bureau - Only for sheep; The first one, 1981; SR-13500; Bureau (Box 203)
          Catalog # PR 403; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-40387-2 SP
        - Burgess, Richard James - Richard James Burgess, 1984; SR-13501; Burgess, Richard James (Box 203)
          Catalog # MLP-15019; A-side Matrix # MLP-1-15019
        - Burgess, Richard James - Breathless, 1984; SR-13502; Burgess, Richard James (Box 203)
          Catalog # V-8591; A-side Matrix # V8591-99347-A-Z1
        - Burke, Solomon - Sidewalks, fences and walls, 1979; SR-13503; Burke, Solomon (Box 203)
          Catalog # L-33-1026; A-side Matrix # L-33-1026A-MT2
          Infinity Record
        - Burning Flames - Me na freard, 1989; SR-13505; Burning Flames (Box 203)
          Catalog # BF-0006; A-side Matrix # DG 0006A
          Burning Flames Music
          Antigua, West Indies
        - Burning Spear - Mek we dweet, 1990; SR-13506; Burning Spear (Box 203)
          Catalog # 539 863-1; A-side Matrix # 162-539-863-1-BS-SP
        - Burrus, Terry - Mighty mouth - (va voom), 1985; SR-13507; Burrus, Terry; Ninety Nine (Box 203)
          Catalog # BP 255; A-side Matrix # BP255A
          Bee Pee Records
        - Burrus, Terry - Love rockin', 1983; SR-13508; Burrus, Terry; Transe (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13509. 2 copies
          Catalog # CP 727; A-side Matrix # CP-727-SA
        - Burrus, Terry - Love rockin', 1983; SR-13509; Burrus, Terry; Transe (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13508. 2 copies
        - Burston & Littlejohn - Rich and famous, 1986; SR-13510; Burston & Littlejohn (Box 203)
          Catalog # 4562 MG; A-side Matrix # 4562-MG-A-67577-15A
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Burton, Arline - Shot in the dark, 1994; SR-13511; Burton, Arline (Box 203)
          Catalog # 44 77473; A-side Matrix # XSS-77473-A
        - Gary Burton Quartet - Seven songs for quartet and chamber orchestra, 1974; SR-13512; Gary Burton Quartet (Box 203)
          Catalog # ECM-1040-ST; A-side Matrix # ST-ECM 1040-A
          ECM Records
        - Burton, Jenny - Do you want it bad enuff, 1986; SR-13513; Burton, Jenny (Box 203)
          Catalog # DMD 986; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-50611-50701-1
        - Burton, Jenny - Dancing for my love, 1985; SR-13514; Burton, Jenny (Box 203)
          Catalog # DMD 861; A-side Matrix # ST DM48152-1
        - Burton, Jenny - Rock steady, 1983; SR-13515; Burton, Jenny (Box 203)
          Catalog # DMD 720; A-side Matrix # STDM 45566-1
        - Richard Burton and Family - 365 wild (tonite), SR-13516; Richard Burton and Family (Box 203)
          Catalog # NAR 759; A-side Matrix # NAR 759 A RE1
          New Age Records
        - Richard Burton and Family - 365 wild (tonite), SR-13517; Richard Burton and Family (Box 203)
        - Burundi Black - Burundi Black, 1981; SR-13518; Burundi Black (Box 203)
          Catalog # BIG 3; A-side Matrix # BIG-3A
          Cachalot Records
        - Burwell, Carter - Scream of love, 1986; SR-13519; Burwell, Carter (Box 203)
          Catalog # MCA-23648; A-side Matrix # MCA-5718-BG-2
        - Bus Boys - American worker, 1982; SR-13520; Bus Boys (Box 203)
          Catalog # AL 9569; A-side Matrix # AL 9569-SA-Z-HRM
        - Bus Boys - Minumum wage rock & roll, 1980; SR-13521; Bus Boys (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13522. 2 copies
          Catalog # AL 5-8232; A-side Matrix # AL5 8232SA-F2
        - Bus Boys - Minumum wage rock & roll, 1980; SR-13522; Bus Boys (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13521. 2 copies. Annotated
        - Busdriver - Get on the bus; Everybody's stylin', 2001; SR-13523; Busdriver (Box 203)
          Catalog # MM09; A-side Matrix # MM-09-A
          Massmen Records
        - Bush Babees - Remember we, 1994; SR-13524; Bush Babees; Da Bush Babees (Box 203)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7049; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7049-A-SRI
        - Bush Babees - Brooklyn movements, 1995; SR-13525; Bush Babees; Da Bush Babees (Box 203)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7884; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7884-A-SRI
        - Bush Babees - The love song (so so def mix), 1996; SR-13526; Bush Babees; Mos Def (Box 203)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8574; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8574-A-SR1
        - Bush Babees - We run things; Original, 1994; SR-13527; Bush Babees; Da Bush Babees (Box 203)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7115; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-7115-SRI
        - Bush Babees - The love song (the remix), 1996; SR-13528; Bush Babees; De La Soul (Box 203)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8504; A-side Matrix # 0-43743-A-PRO-A-8504-A-SRI
        - Bush Babees - Gravity, 1996; SR-13529; Bush Babees (Box 203)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8561; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-8561-A-SRI
        - Bushwacka! - Monster, 2000; SR-13530; Bushwacka! (Box 203)
          Catalog # PLANK015; A-side Matrix # PLANK 015 A
          Plank Records
        - Bushwacka! - The Egyptian, 2001; SR-13531; Bushwacka! (Box 203)
          Catalog # PLANK018; A-side Matrix # PLANK-018-A1
        - Bushwick Bill - Who's the biggest, 1995; SR-13532; Bushwick Bill (Box 203)
          Catalog # SPRO-38479; A-side Matrix # Y-38479-A
        - Bushwick Bill - Sex on the floor, SR-13533; Bushwick Bill (Box 203)
          Catalog # 40401; A-side Matrix # NUW-40401-A
          Nu Wave Entertainment
        - Bushwick Bill - Only god knows, 1995; SR-13534; Bushwick Bill (Box 203)
          Catalog # SPRO-11030; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11030-A
        - Busta Flex - Busta flex (Disc one), 1998; SR-13535; Busta Flex (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13536. Double album
          Catalog # 3984-22188-1; A-side Matrix # 3984221881 A 1
          WEA Music
        - Busta Flex - Busta flex (Disc two), 1998; SR-13536; Busta Flex (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13535. Double album
          Catalog # 3984-22188-1; A-side Matrix # 3984221881 C 1
        - Busta Funk - I need money; Funkadelicious, 1998; SR-13537; Busta Funk (Box 203)
          Catalog # FTONE010; A-side Matrix # F TONE 010 A2
          Funky Tone
        - Busta Funk - Black sugar, 1998; SR-13538; Busta Funk (Box 203)
          Catalog # FTONE020; A-side Matrix # F TONE 020 A1
        - Busta Rhymes - Dangerous; Club banger; I never thought, 1997; SR-13539; Busta Rhymes (Box 203)
          Catalog # 7559-63878-0; A-side Matrix # 755 963878-0-A
        - Busta Rhymes - Pass the courvoisier part II, 2002; SR-13540; Busta Rhymes; P. Diddy; Diddy, 1969-; Williams, Pharell (Box 203)
          Catalog # 80813-21154-1; A-side Matrix # J1PV-21154-1SA
        - Busta Rhymes - Make it clap, 2002; SR-13541; Busta Rhymes; Spliff Star (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13542. 2 copies
          Catalog # J1PV 21236-1; A-side Matrix # J1PV-21236-1SA
        - Busta Rhymes - Make it clap, 2002; SR-13542; Busta Rhymes; Spliff Star (Box 203)
          In same jacket as # SR-13541. 2 copies
        - Busta Rhymes - Anarchy (Disc one), 2000; SR-13543; Busta Rhymes (Box 203)